localsearch.ae 2018-07-23

# Privacy Policy - LocalSearch.ae

**Privacy and Security Policy**

This Privacy and Security Policy addresses the privacy of visitors to the [LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/) website. It identifies the type of data and information **LocalSearch.ae** collects from visitors, how we use and disclose it, and the steps we take to secure your privacy. 

**Information Collection**

**LocalSearch.ae** collects personal information when you become a Registered User with [LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/), when you use [LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/) products and services, when you visit [LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/) pages, and when you enter promotions or contests. 

We may also collect non-personal information about your visit, such as the domain name and the name of the web page from which you entered our site, how much time you spend on each page, and the IP address associated with your computer. This information is used to improve the performance and operation of the website.  

When you become a Registered User, we ask for information such as your name, birth date, gender, country, city, phone numbers and email address. 

[LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/) automatically receives and records information on our server from your browser, including your IP address, [LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/) cookie information, and any page you request. 

[LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/) uses the information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, complete your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, and/or provide statistical reporting for internal and external customers.  

**Your Account Information**

You can edit your [LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/) Account Information at any time. By becoming a Registered User, you agree to receive select information from **LocalSearch.ae** and its partners.    

**Internet Cookies and Related Technologies**

We may use cookies to improve the content delivered to you while you are on our website. Cookies do not contain or capture any personal information but it may capture computer identification information. Your decision to refuse cookies from [LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/) will not prevent you from using our site, but may limit your ability to take advantage of some of our advanced features. 

Some pages of the website may use computer code called "one-pixel gifs," "clear gifs," or "Web beacons" which are embedded in web pages to monitor the activity on our website. This technology does not capture or contain any of your personal information. 

**Third Party Advertisers and External Links**

The [LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/) website contains advertisements from third-party advertisers or provides links to external websites. **LocalSearch.ae** is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. Our partners or advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on our site. These third parties may place cookies on your browser when you visit our site. Any third party cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the company placing them. 

**Information Disclosed To Third Parties**

**LocalSearch.ae** may use aggregated information about how visitors use our web site and disclose this information with our partners and related third parties in order to improve our website and attract advertisers and listings. For example, we may share how many individuals visit the website and on average how long they stay on each page. Such use and sharing of aggregated information does not disclose any of your personal information to third parties.  

**LocalSearch.ae** does not rent, sell, disclose or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products, services, or information you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

 **LocalSearch.ae** does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view an ad. 

**Security**

**LocalSearch.ae** takes your security seriously and takes reasonable steps to protect your information. No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any firewalls or secure server software we may employ. 

**LocalSearch.ae** continues to evaluate and implement enhancements in security technology and practices; however we can only take steps to help reduce the risks of unauthorized access.  

By using this website or providing personal information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this site.  

**Secure Socket Layer (SSL)**

**LocalSearch.ae** uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting certain kinds of information, such as payment information. An icon resembling a padlock is displayed on the bottom of most browsers window during SSL transactions that involve credit cards and other forms of payment. 

Any time **LocalSearch.ae** asks you for credit card information for payment or for verification purposes on [LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/), the information will be accepted via SSL encryption. 

The credit card information you provide will not be stored on the servers of **LocalSearch.ae** The information is stored on the servers of the payment gateway provider which are secure and strictly compliant with PCI compliance norms. This is entirely for security and safety purposes. Once you choose to store or enter your credit card number on [LocalSearch.ae](http://localsearch.ae/), it will be used for one-time use only and you will need to enter the credit card information again during your subsequent payment transaction. 

**Secure Storage**

**LocalSearch.ae** maintains reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. 

**Privacy and Security Policy Updates**

This Privacy and Security Policy supersedes and replaces all previously posted Privacy and Security Policies. **LocalSearch.ae** reserves the right to update this Privacy and Security Policy to reflect any changes at any time.
